Hi folks!

Iam **HEMNATH**

29 year old Profoundly skilled male designer with high proficiency in visual design.

Visual Designer

With 7.5 years of Design Experience









Proffessional Skills



User Experience Designer

Understanding User needs / Competitor Analysis / Creating Persona / Information Architecture / Creating Wire frames.



User Interface Designer

Defining Color themes / Typography / Icons / Illustrations / UI screens / Marketing collaterals.



User Interface Developer

Converting PSD to HTML Layout / image optimization / CSS styling / Creating Font icons / Animation using CSS and JQUERY.

Software Skills















Experience Summary

Studio



Studio 45

2009 - 2011

Designer

Roles & Responsiblities

Creating Flash Templates, Illustrations, Website, 2d animations, Marketing collaterals, Logo design, Icons, Brouchers, Posters, Corporate presentations, E- Learning modules etc.





Element K

2011 - 2012

Art & Media Developer

Roles & Responsiblities

E - Learning, Localization, Flash Templates, 2d animations, Illustrations, Icons, Image Optimization, Flash Presentations, Mailer designs etc.





Object Frontier Software

2012 - 2015

Design Engineer

Roles & Responsiblities

Marketing collatrals,
Website design, PPT
Presentations, Illustrations,
User experience design,
E- Books, Mailers, Posters,
Font icons, User Interface,
HTML convertions, CSS
stylings, Media query etc.





Zoho Corporation

2015 - Till Date

Visual Designer

Roles & Responsiblities

User experience design,
User Interface, HTML
convertions, CSS stylings,
E- Books, Mailer
template,SVG illustrations,
Font icons, CSS animations,
Front end bug fixing etc.

Education

BSC Viscom

DGVC College (Chennai)

2006 - 2009

ST Marys Matric

Higher Secondry School (Chennai)



AutoDesk
Certification in 3ds Max

Hobbies & Intrests







Sketching

Photography

Art Crafts

Personal Info

Name Hemnath.H

Gender Male

Date of birth 07 september 1988

Marital Status Married

Location Chennai

Contact Info



9791106538



hemnath21@gmail.com